[TOY BLARING MUSIC]
Oh, for God sakes.
[MUSIC STOPS]
(Leonard:)So you have childhood issues.
(Leonard:)We all have childhood issues.
(Leonard:)At some point, you just need to grow up
and get past them.
TOY:
Fire. Fire.
[LASER SOUND EFFECTS FIRING]
Leonard, let me handle this. Please?
-Fire, fire.
-Look, let-- She--
[TOY CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
[TOY STOPS]
Sheldon, please try and understand.
Look, Leonard and I are in a relationship
and occasionally we're gonna fight.
But no matter what happens
between us, we will always love you.
Right, Leonard?
(Leonard:)Always is a long time.
(Leonard:)Sure. Always.
(Penny:)You know, how about we buy you
this robot and then we all go home?
(Sheldon:)I want that one.
(Penny:)Okay, you can have that one.
(Leonard:)Oh, come on.
He's just gonna play with it twice...